<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThirtyDaysOfExercise</string>
    <string name="title_1">MN Pork arms + Abs</string>
    <string name="title_2">Legs superset</string>
    <string name="title_3">Legs plus back</string>
    <string name="title_4">Strength-Cardio plus kick boxing</string>
    <string name="title_5">Chest plus Arms</string>
    <string name="title_6">MN Beef and Full Body Pyramid</string>
    <string name="title_7">Legs plus Butt</string>
    <string name="title_8">MN Beef HIIT Circuit</string>
    <string name="title_9">Cardio plus Abs</string>


    <string name = "description_1">
        Start standing feet shoulder-width distance apart knees slightly bent, holding a single
        dumbbell at your chest (vertically so dumbbell is touching your collarbone and sternum).
        Lower down into a squat position, lowering your hips down parallel with your knees. Drive
        your knees out toward your outer three toes.
    </string>


    <string name = "description_2">
        Stand with feet hip-width apart, knees slightly bent. Hold one dumbbell in your left hand,
        in front of your hip (palm is facing in towards your body).Stagger your feet, so your right
        leg is slightly in front of your left foot. Kickstand your back left foot, left heel
        floating off the ground. Keep 80% of your weight in your front foot, 20% in your back left
        toe.
    </string>

    <string name = "description_3">
        Start standing, feet wider than shoulder-width (lateral squat stance), with toes facing
        forward or slightly turned out.Sit your hips back, bending your right knee while leaving
        your left leg straight. Think of performing a single leg squat with your right leg while
        your left leg remains straight. Dumbbell comes to the inside of the right foot; knees and
        toes are pointing forward.
    </string>

    <string name = "description_4">
        Stand with feet shoulder-width apart, holding a set of dumbbells in your hands with palms
        facing in towards each other.With a soft bend in the knees, hinge at your hips to lower
        your torso as you slide the dumbbells down in front of your legs. Think about pushing
        your hips back behind you. Hinge until you feel a stretch in the back of your front
        legs (hamstrings).
    </string>

    <string name = "description_5">
        Start in an athletic stance or loaded squat position, with your feet shoulder-width distance
        apart and a slight bend in your knees.With your chest upright and your core engaged, “jack”
        your feet out into a wide squat (feet are wider than your shoulders).Start in a high plank
        position with your shoulders stacked over your wrists. Option to place your hands on weights
        if you have wrist pain.Hold this plank position, maintaining a straight
       line with your body, gaze slightly in front of you.

    </string>


    <string name = "description_6">
   Stand with your feet hip-width apart, knees slightly bent.Hinge at the hips until your torso
        is parallel to the floor (neck in line with your spine, flat back, and belly button and
        rib cage pulled in).
    </string>

    <string name = "description_7">
        Stand with your feet slightly wider than shoulder-width apart, knees bent, holding a
        dumbbell in each hand at your sides, palms facing in towards one another.Extend your
        right arm overhead, locking out the elbow and keeping your bicep by your right ear.
    </string>

    <string name = "description_8">
        Start standing on the right side of your mat with your feet shoulder-width apart.
        Perform two single high knees as you move laterally to the left, driving your right
        knee up to hip-height, then your left knee. Core is engaged.
    </string>

    <string name = "description_9">
        Start in a high plank position with your shoulders stacked over your wrists.Hold
        plank as you perform a shoulder tap, tapping the left shoulder with the right hand
        and then the right shoulder with the left hand. While keep hips square and stable
        to the mat.
    </string>


</resources>